Hi, in this lesson, you will improve how numbers are handled and displayed in your calculate.
So, of course, you'll add a limit of 10 digits in total. If I enter an amount,
you'll see I can enter as much digits as I want, and it's much bigger than the calculator display.
So, and mostly it's not real numbers, yeah.
Build, we'll limit it to 10 digits, the digits before decimal, before the dot, and after the decimal
in total of 10 digits. This prevents user from entering unreleased to take the long numbers
and keeps the display clear and readable. You'll also show a message when the limit is reached,
so user will be notified that he can't pipe more digits. It will be small hemed, but it will be useful.
So, in general, this improvement improves usability and prevents some display overflow.
Next, we will format the large numbers with a view of x-space.
This just after decimal, you will see that it's difficult to read how much thousands have.
And we'll format the large numbers with a space between thousands, like a view at a space right here,
and here. So, this change makes numbers much easier to read. You'll see that you have, for example,
88, 88, 88, 88, 88, you'll have a separator as a space right here up.
And it will be much easier to read for calculations, and you'll look more professional.
So, but then that's also awesome, calculator will be much more professional, and of course,
user friendly. So, let's get started. And I prepared the prompt to limit digits, maximum number of digits.
I'll ask AI to limit it up to 10 total digits, digits before and after decimal in total,
and when the limit is reached, the block extra characters but still allow backspace in editing.
So, we'll block user from entering more digits than is allowed.
And we will allow user to remove these digits, of course, that like. We'll also short the short message,
as I told you, and it will be disappeared after three seconds. So, let's run this prompt,
and see what the result will be. So, as more details, you will give to AI, in your prompt,
the more accurate result you will get. So, always, if you know some edge cases or some
small details, always describe them in the prompt. Okay, let's see if I update the calculator
of the block digits. Okay, here's still syncing, I guess. Yes, it's still syncing. Okay, now we
see, we ended up updating this way. Okay, here's the message. Okay, and in the use calculator,
here's the message time mode, here's the message digits. Okay, it's still working,
and also better the application, and just add a message. So, let's now see how it works.
I go and there are more digits, so maximum 10 digits. Okay, it's fine. Yep, it looks correct.
So, I can backspace, and for example, we have 10 digits. Let's add, yep, we can add more digits. So,
it looks good. I like it. Oh, let's now format the varish numbers at a thousand separator.
Oh, I will paste my next prompt. I will click keep to keep all the changes, close the files.
We don't need it. So, my next prompt is format large numbers in the display by adding a space
as a thousand separator. I show an example how I'd like to format it. I also ask apply
format and dynamically as user types, or when showing the result. So, and also ensure
formatting doesn't affect calculations of stoichiometric values.
After I make font, font, size, and bit, smaller. So, let's make it smaller because if you add a thousand
separator, it will go much bigger, and the patterns will be too small from the left side.
Okay, let's run it.
So, we see the outer model also looks good for these changes, but we have some limitations in
the free plan. Okay, it's adding some logic to format numbers. So, we have now a big function,
but no worry. Okay, the red gets at the check it. So, I'm not going to dive into what AI
added. That was the logic. So, the font size is smaller. Okay, it's fine. And the display,
yeah, we just use a format number. Ideally, you can use some libraries, some npm libraries,
the format numbers, you can ask AI like use a give. For example, we can ask, did so,
we will do it in the next one, I guess. We will use, we will do an investigation of thought,
formatting libraries we might use, and then we'll apply one just to not have a lot of custom code we
need to support and test. So, it finished. Let's click keep and check how it works. So, we see
it's formatted. I will start typing. Let me see, plus.
Okay, we can, plus something, plus.
Okay, cool. And I feel it's wrong.
Last. So, all we need to do one more fix. If the first part of a calculation that felt the
the first number is as tendages, we cannot enter anything up to the sign. So, we need to fix it.
A user is not able to enter another digit, another amount after he entered the first
amount as then digits in thought. And click it on operator bottom. So, we'll ask AI to fix it.
Because it's not okay. So, let's see if he can fix it.
Yeah, he understand it's a bug. He'll update an input digit logic.
Oh, let's see what he did waiting for operand.
Okay, you can just move it to another place. So, I hope it will work. Let's try again.
Plus. So, yeah, it looks it works. So, let's not try to calculate some big digits. We want to
multiply and just I'm curious how the result will be shown. Okay, it's fine. It's displayed in
into lines. So, I like it. Okay, that's great. So, in this lesson, you learn how to apply
different fixes to improve logic with AI. You even see that we can ask some follow-up questions
about the prompts we asked before. So, when an AI will do the fixes. And see you in the next
lesson. Where we will investigate what formatting libraries we can use do not have a lot of custom
code and use some code which is tested by community. So, see you in the next lesson.